Margarita Mazo Old Believer and Molokan collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Margarita Mazo Old Believer and Molokan collection 1973-2020 1980-2004
AFC 2022/003
Mazo, Margarita
approximately 7,213 items
approximately 4,188 documents
110 document files (WPD, DOCX, RTF, ASC, TXT): digital
325 sound cassettes: analog
69 sound cassettes (DAT): digital
23 video cassettes (VHS): analog
2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35mm
859 photographs: film negatives, color; 35mm
4 photographs: film negatives, color; 120mm
419 photographs: color slides; 35mm
1,165 photographs: prints, color; various sizes
48 photographs: prints, black and white; various sizes
1 floppy disk: digital; 3 1/2 in.
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of field recordings and photographs from ethnomusicologist Margarita Mazo's fieldwork with Molokan and Old Believer communities in Russia, Poland, and the United States. Also included are Mazo's academic research files and materials from her work for two Smithsonian Folklife Festivals.
Provenance
Margarita Mazo; Purchase; 2021.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Access and Restrictions
The Margarita Mazo Old Believer and Molokan collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Biographical Note
Margarita Mazo is a professor emerita at the Ohio State University, where she founded a program in Cognitive Ethnomusicology. She holds a PhD from the Leningrad (St. Petersburg) Conservatory where her research focused on Russian music. She has held teaching positions at the Leningrad (St. Petersburg) Conservatory, the New England Conservatory of Music, and Harvard University.
Scope and Content
Collection of field recordings, photographs, and manuscripts created by ethnomusicologist Margarita Mazo. Mazo's research and fieldwork focuses on two sects of Spiritual Christians that split from the Russian Orthodox Church: Molokans and Old Believers. Mazo's research explores music and religious expression for these two religious sects and the ways diasporic communities maintain and adapt traditions. The collection includes documentation of Molokan and Old Believer communities in Stavropol, Tula, and Moscow, Russia and in Poland as well as diasporic Molokan and Old Believer communities in California, Oregon, and Pennsylvania in the United States.
Mazo was also involved with planning two Smithsonian Festivals of American Folklife. In 1988, Mazo was the Program Curator for the Music from the Peoples of the Soviet Union portion of the Festival and in 1995, she was one of the curators for the Russian Roots, American Branches portion of the Festival. Planning documents, photographs, and recordings from her work with the Festivals are included in the collection. Also included are Mazo's academic research files on Molokans and Old Believers as well as article drafts, correspondence, and other administrative or academic files.
Arrangement
The Margarita Mazo Old Believer and Molokan collection is organized in 9 series:
Series 1: Festival of American Folklife, Washington, D.C., 1988-1995
Series 2: Stavropol, Russia fieldwork, 1988-2020 (bulk: 1988-1990)
Series 3: California and Oregon fieldwork, 1990-2020 (bulk: 1990-1995)
Series 4: Tula and Moscow, Russia fieldwork, 1987-1994
Series 5: Poland fieldwork, 1992
Series 6: Erie, Pennsylvania fieldwork, 1983-2018 (bulk: 1995-1998)
Series 7: Mirovaya Festival, Russia
Series 8: Academic files, 1973-2018
Series 9: Miscellany, 1988-1993
The Festival and fieldwork series are divided into subseries by date of the research trip. Materials are organized within each subseries by material format. Sara Ludewig transcribed folder titles as they appeared on the original folder. In cases where there was no title on the original folder, Ludewig supplied a title which appears in brackets.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Mazo, Margarita
Organizations
Festival of American Folklife (1988: Washington, D.C.); Festival of American Folklife (1995: Washington, D.C.)
Subjects
Christian sects--Poland.; Christian sects--Russia.; Folk festivals--Russia.; Folk festivals--United States.; Molokans--Liturgy.; Molokans.; Music--Religious aspects.; Old Believers--Liturgy.; Old Believers.; Russian diaspora.; Russians--California.; Russians--Oregon.; Russians--Pennsylvania.
Form/Genre
Field recordings.; Manuscripts.; Photographs.; Sound recordings.; Video recordings.
Container List
- Series 1: Festival of American Folklife, Washington, D.C.
  - Subseries 1: 1988 Festival
    Mazo was a Program Curator for the Music from the Peoples of the Soviet Union portion of the 1988 Smithsonian Folklife Festival. The Festival featured musicians and performers from the Soviet Union who participated in an exchange with American musicians who later traveled to Russia to perform.
    - Audio and video
      - Podserednee #1, June 29, 1988, AFC 2022/003: SR001; 1 sound cassette
      - Podserednee #2, June 29, 1988, AFC 2022/003: SR002; 1 sound cassette
      - Veronika Pavilionese (cont.) Podserednee #1, July 5, 1988, AFC 2022/003: SR003; 1 sound cassette
      - Podserednee #2, July 5, 1988, AFC 2022/003: SR004; 1 sound cassette
      - Podserednee #3, July 5, 1988, AFC 2022/003: SR005; 1 sound cassette
      - Podserednee #4, #1, July 5-6, 1988, AFC 2022/003: SR006; 1 sound cassette
      - Podserednee, July 7, 1988, AFC 2022/003: SR007; 1 sound cassette
      - Podserednee Yl'ana Kot, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR008; 1 sound cassette
      - Podserednee, Veronika Pavilionese, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR009; 1 sound cassette
      - Am. Molokans: 1. Ia obratilsia, 2. Gospod' pastyr' (4:55), 3. Ia (?) (7:33), 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV001; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - At wedding: 1. Erie chant (Nekrasovtsy sing along), 2. Nekrasovtsy chant, 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV002; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Erie: 1. Resurrection (English), 2. Syncopated English/Slavonic, 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV003; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Molokan Obed.: 1. Vidayutsya (psalm), 2. Matreng and doll (1:32), 3. Psalm together, 4. Lapsha (5:33), 5. Prayer and predstanem my (6:31), 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV004; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Narrative Café: 1. Verdian, 2. Samarin, 3. Belikov, 4. (3:21) Primer and a question, 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV005; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Nekrasovtsy dance with audience, 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV006; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Nekrasovtsy, Erie: 1. Wedding song and Lauert Nekrasovtsy, 2. Smoke 2:50, 3. Lazar (6:01), 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV007; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Nekrasovtsy: 1. Marusia in dress, introduction, 2. 4 men, Vsponni (brief), 3. Marfa Khodils in devochha poborochku, 4. Michael Poshli devhi na rabotu, 5. Marusia sings, 6. New York man, 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV008; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Nekrosovtsy: 1. Turkish dance, 2. Turkish song, 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV009; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Nekrasovtsy: 1. Vladimir, 2. Krylo, 3. Lullaby, 4. Po senian, 5. 4 women, 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV010; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Nekrasovtsy wedding: 1. At the bride (2 songs), 2. Best men before the posad and posad (3:06), 3. Procession with shell, 4. Boyara (6:03), 5. Kichka (7:15), 6. Women sing and men dance with garmoshla (9:00), 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV011; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Russian Molokans 2 psalms (2 starts at 2:19), 1988, AFC 2022/003: MV012; 1 video cassette (VHS)
    - Manuscripts
      Correspondence, planning documents, field notes, and publicity from the 1988 Festival.
      - Festival documents, 1988, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Festival publicity, 1988, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Folklore festivals, Washington, 1988, See also AFC 2022/033: PH028; 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Song in Rural Russia, 1988 Festival of American Folklife, 1988, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/4)
      - [Soviet-American folklife project], 1987-1988, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/5)
      - [With singers from Podserednye village, Smithsonian Folklife Festival photo], 1988, Photo printed on foam board.; 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Negatives, slides, and photographic prints
      - Folklore festivals Washington, 1988, 3 color negatives (120mm); AFC 2022/003: PH028 (Box 17)
      - Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 1988, 4 color prints (4x6 in.) (Box 11)
      - Washington, 1987, 8 black-and-white prints (8x10 in.) (Box 12)
  - Subseries 2: 1995 Festival
    Mazo was one of the curators for the Russian Roots, American Branches: Music in Two Worlds portion of the 1995 Smithsonian Folklife Festival. The Festival featured musicians from Russia, the Ukraine, and other former Soviet republics as well as musicians from Old Believer and Molokan communities in the United States.
    - Audio and video
      - Russian Music Stage, June 23, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR010; Side A: I. American Molokans (Conclusion #6), II. Narrative: Old Believers (Nekrasovtsky) immigration stories, III. Russian Molokans (P.1); Side B: I. Russian Molokans (cont.), II. American Old Believers (Part 1 of 2).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 23, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR011; Side A: I. American Old Believers (Part 2 of 2), II. Learn Old Believer song; Side B: I. Narrative: Transition of Molokan musical traditions (American Molokan transmission of music), II. Nekrasovtsky Old Believers (Part 1 of 2).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 23, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR012; Side A: I. Nekrasovtsky Old Believers (Part 2 of 2).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 24, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR013; Side A: I. Russian Molokans; Side B: I. Russian music narrative preservation of traditions Old Believers.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 24, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR014; Side A: Russian Roots: Old Believers (cont.); Side B: Russian Roots.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 24, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR015; Side A: Russian music, learn Old Believers song, American Molokans; Side B: Russian music, American Molokans (cont.), Russian Molokans.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 24, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR016; Side A: Russian music, Russian Molokans, Russian and American Old Believers; Side B: Russian music, Russian and American Old Believers (cont.); 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 24, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR017; Side A: Russian music American Old Believers (cont.); 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 25, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR018; Side A: Act I, American and Nekrasovtsky Old Believers rituals, narrative; Side B: Act 1 (cont.), Act II beginning Old Believers wedding feast.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 25, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR019; Side A: Act II (cont.), Old Believers wedding feast; Side B: Act II (cont.), Old Believers wedding feast.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 25, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR020; Side A: Act II (cont.), Old Believers wedding feast; Side B: Act II (cont.), Old Believers wedding feast, Act III, American Molokan textile traditions, Act IV, Beginning American Old Believers.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 25, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR021; Side A: Act IV (cont.), American Old Believers, Act V, American Molokans; Side B: Act V (cont.), American Molokans, Act VI, Learn an American Molokan song, Act VII, Russian Molokan.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 25, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR022; Side A: Act VII (cont.), Russian Molokans.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 30, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR023; Side A: American Molokans Act I; Side B: American Molokan Act I (cont.), American Old Believers Act II, American Old Believers Act III rituals and celebration.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 30, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR024; Side A: Act III (cont.), Old Believers (American) "Rituals and celebration," Act IV, Russian Molokan; Side B: Act IV (cont.), Russian Molokan, American Molokan and Russian Molokan together, Act V, Learn Russian Molokan song.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 30, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR025; Side A: Act VI, Russian Old Believer Stavropol; Side B: Act VII, American Molokan San Francisco.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 30, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR026; Side A: Act VIII, American Old Believers Erie, PA; Side B: Act IX, Russian Molokan Stavropol, Russia.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, June 30, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR027; Side A: Russian Old Believers.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 2, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR028; Combined Acts I and II, American and Russia Molokans "Rituals and celebration" and "Feasts."; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 2, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR029; Combined Acts I and II, American and Russia Molokans "Rituals and celebration" and "Feasts."; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 2, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR030; Side A: Act III, Nekrasovtsy Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia); Side B: Act III (cont.), Nekrasovtsy Old Believers.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 2, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR031; Side A: Act IV, Narrative: Textile traditions (American Molokans San Francisco, CA), Act V, American Old Believers (Erie, PA); Side B: Act V (cont.), American Old Believers (Erie, PA), Act VI, (Erie, PA) American Old Believers, Narrative: Preservation and adaptation of traditions.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 2, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR032; Side A: Act VI (cont.), Narrative: Preservation and adaptation of traditions (American Old Believers Erie, PA), Act VII, Nekrasovsty Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 3, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR033; Side A: Act I, American Molokans (San Francisco, CA); Side B: Act I (cont.), American Molokans (San Francisco, CA), Act II, American Old Believers (Erie, PA).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 3, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR034; Side A: Act III, Learn an Old Believers song (Fr. Pimen Simon, Erie, PA), Act IV, Narrative: Molokan rituals and celebration Russian Molokan (Stavropol, RU); Side B: Act IV (cont.), Narrative Russian Molokans; Act V, Nekrasovtsy Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 3, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR035; Side A: Act V (cont.), Nekrasovsty Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia), Act VI, Narrative: "Preservation and adaptation of traditions" (Russian and American Molokans); Side B: Act VII, Russian Molokans (Stavropol, Russia).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 3, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR036; Side A: American Old Believers (Erie, PA); Side B: Festival encounters, traditional culture in a post Communist world, V. Merta-Praha, Cz Rep., G. Beliko-Stavropol, RU, M. Shchetinkina-Stavropol, RU.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 3, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR037; Side A: American Molokans (San Francisco, CA).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 4, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR038; Side A: Act I, Nekrasovsty Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia); Side B: Act I (cont.), Nekrasovtsy Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia), Act II, Narrative Old Believers migration stories: (Nekrasovtsy Old Believers) Stavropol, Russia.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 4, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR039; Side A: Act V, Transmission of Old Believers music traditions - narrative, American Old Believers Erie, PA; Side B: Act V (cont.), Act VI, American Molokans San Francisco.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 4, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR040; Side A: Act III, Russian Molokans (Stavropol, Russia); Side B: Act IV, Learn a Molokan song (learning session), Act V, Transmission of Old Believers musical traditions (American Old Believers) Erie, PA.; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 4, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR041; Side A: Act VIII, Russian Molokans (Stavropol, Russia) (women only); Side B: Act IX, Nekrasovtsy Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia).; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian Music Stage, July 4, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR042; Side A: Act IX (cont.), Nekrasovsty Old Believers (Stavropol, Russia), Act X, Closing session (All groups on the stage together); Side B: Act X concludes.; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, June 22, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR043; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR044; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR045; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR046; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR047; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR048; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR049; 1 sound cassette
      - Washington-95, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR050; 1 sound cassette
      - DC group Spevka #1, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR051; 1 sound cassette
      - Russian music, June 26, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR052; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian music, June 26, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR053; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian music, June 26, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR054; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian music, June 26, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR055; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, June 27, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR056; Act I - Russian Molokans, Act II - American Old Believers, Act III - Narrative (Russian Molokans) "Preservation and adaption of traditions."; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, June 27, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR057; Act IV - American Molokans, Act V - "Learn to sing a Molokan song" American Molokans.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, June 27, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR058; Act VI - Russian Molokans, Act VII - Nekrasovsty Old Believers.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, June 27, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR059; Act VIII - Narrative - Old Believers "Fasting, feasts, and St's days," Act IX - American Molokans.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, July 1, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR060; Act I - American Molokans, Act II - Learn a Molokan song, Act III - American and Nekrasovtsy Old Believers.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, July 1, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR061; Act III (cont.) - American and Nekrasovtsy Old Believers, Act IV - Molokan migration stories.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, July 1, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR062; Act V - Russian Molokans, Act VI - Textile traditions.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Russian Music Stage, July 1, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR063; Act VII - Russian Molokans, Act VIII - Nekrasovtsy Old Believers.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Washington D.C. American Folklife 1995 Molokan Sobranie, June 25, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR064; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Washington 1995 Nekrasovtsy, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR065; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - SF 40462 Old Believers original master, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR066; Possibly a master tape left by Margarita Mazo.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Manuscripts
      Correspondence, planning documents, field notes, and publicity from the 1995 Festival.
      - 1995 Festival of American Folklife: Russian Roots, American Branches, 1995, afc2022003_dc002; Transcripts, reports, academic papers, correspondence, and written remarks from the 1995 Smithsonian Folklife Festival. Original floppy disk is housed in Box-Folder 8/21.; 12 digital manuscripts (DOCX) from 1 floppy disk (3.5 in.)
      - AFL, 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Festival, 1995, See also AFC 2022/003: PH029 and afc2022003_dc002.; 1 folder of manuscript materials; includes 1 color print (5x7 in.) and 1 black-and-white print (8x10 in.) (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Festival, 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/9)
      - [Festival notes], 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Field notes and correspondence, 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Letters from performers, 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Molokans and Old Believers in Two Worlds, 1995 Festival of American Folklife, 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/13)
      - [Russian Music Stage cassette index], 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Smithsonian Festival, 1992-1995, 2003, afc2022003_dc001; Reports written by Mazo and planning documents from the 1995 Smithsonian Folklife Festival in Washington, D.C.; 8 digital manuscripts (WPD)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife award], 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/OS 1)
    - Negatives, slides, and photographic prints
      - Capitol, 1995, 25 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH032_001 - PH032_025 (Box 15)
      - Erie/O.B. and Nevr., July 1995, 13 color negatives (35mm); 13 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH013 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - Festival, 1995, 1 color negative (120mm); AFC 2022/003: PH029 (Box 17)
      - Festival, 1995, 3 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH033_001 - PH003_003 (Box 15)
      - Festival 95, 1995, 37 color negatives (35mm); 37 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH015 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Folklife festival], 1995, 5 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH034_001 - PH0034_005 (Box 15)
      - Library of Congress and social dance, 1995, 25 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH036_001 - PH036_025 (Box 15)
      - LOC Festival, 1995, 25 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH035_001 - PH035_025 (Box 15)
      - Nekrsovtsy last day/hotel, 1995, 48 color negatives (35mm); 22 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH014 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - O.B. Hinpucol, 1995, 25 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH037_001 - PH037_025 (Box 15)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], June 1, 1995, 25 color negatives (35mm); 19 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH016 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 37 color negatives (35mm); 36 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH001 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 25 color negatives (35mm); 25 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH002 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 25 color negatives (35mm); 25 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH003 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 8 color negatives (35mm); 36 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH006 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 25 color negatives (35mm); 25 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH007 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 25 color negatives (35mm); 36 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH008 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 26 color negatives (35mm); 15 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH009 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 25 color negatives (35mm); 25 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH010 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 13 color negatives (35mm); 13 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH012 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], July 1995, 87 color negatives (35mm); 92 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH018 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], 1995, 2 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH004 (Box 17)
      - [Smithsonian Folklife Festival], 1995, 27 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH005 (Box 17)